# Veena Kamurti

Full stack developer

**Phone**: 9322298605

Email: veena98.kamurti@gmail.com

Site: uniquedeveloper.wixsite.com/veenakamurti

**Git**:/kamurtiveena

Pen : https://codepen.io/v\_stack

#### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Full stacker with over 3 years of experience in MEAN and MERN Full Stack Development. Recognized consistently for commendable performer and contributions to success in IT industry. Experience in Research and high level documentation under how Technology pace is moving. Reskilling in cloud area.

## **SKILLS**

- Languages: Javascript, Java,
   Basic Python, Typescript.
- UI: Angular and React
- Database: Omnisci
   DB,MongoDB, PostgreSQL.
- Cache : Elastic Search, Redis
- Testing Frameworks : Chai, Mocha, Jasmine
- **Tools:** VsCode, Eclipse, Postman, Swagger.
- Frameworks: Node, Express, Spring boot, Superset, React-spring, Material UI. Open Source Contribution:
- Apache superset custom plugins

# **ACCOMPLISHMENTS**

- RnR Award in DC Technical events management Infy'21
- Winner in Ideathon in Medlyey Hyderabad infosys July' 21
- STG Excellence Ninja Award for Q1-2022 Infosys'
- Winner in women hackathon in Hyderabad infosys Jan' 21

#### TRAININGS AND CERTIFICATIONS

- Sping Boot Beginner from udemy
- TCS-iON Certification
  Career Edge Knockdown the Lockdown
  credential ID 5-7031732-1016
- National level NPTEL Online Certification
   IIT Kharagpur, Mumbai
   Scored 80% in 'C++', 65% in 'OperatingSystem'
   73%in'DBMS', 50% in 'Python'

#### OTHER TECHNOLOGIES

- IOT, Big Data & Hadoop ,Ethical Hacking attended Workshop in IIT Bombay, IISC Bangalore
- React+Redux, HTML, JavaScript, Python, PHP, Java, SQL, Devops (Completed courses in Solo Learn)

### **EDUCATION**

Walchand institute of technology, Solapur – 2019
BACHELOR OF ENGINEERING- Computer Science

**Government Polytechnic, Solapur – 2016** High School Diploma **INTERSTS** 

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### **Senior System Engineer**

Credex Technology- Sept 2021 to present

- Working as Full stack developer in MERN stack
- Excelled knowledge in Telecom sector
- Working on Testing frameworks additionally

## Promoted as Specialist Programmer in Q2-2022, Infosys

#### **Digital Specialist Engineer**

Infosys, Hyderabad - Jan 2021 to Sept 2021

 Worked as open source contributor in Apache superset building custom plugins and chart visualization of csv data inserted in postgreSQL.

## **Specialist System Engineer**

Infosys, Hyderabad - July 2019 to Dec 2020

- Researcher Under high level findings for Technology Trends, Future is AI, Open source for innovation.
- Full stack developer With United Airlines migrated flight booking application In Angular9 with Material UI and .Net .
- Hoopla shopping site Developed SPA(single page application) in MERN stack following Agile scrum.
   Designed mongo DB database and used microservice architecture to achieve scalability.
   Used Redux along with react for intuitive UX and material theme for designing UI
- Selected through HackWithInfy-2018. Trained and working in MEAN/ MERN stack. I was part of specialist team which is responsible for fast paced development and delivery of client critical applications. I got chance to contribute in DC events-Tech Team.

# **PROFESSIONAL SKILLS**

- Good Communication Skills with Understanding & Analyzing capability
- Leadership qualities, Solution Oriented, Positive approach
- Always ready to help, solution oriented
- Sharing Knowlegde, Believe in Team work
- Design Thinking, Strategic Thinking
- Quick learner, Coder

Singing, Dancing, Travelling, Social work, Reading Motivational Books & watching web series